Marlon Riggs Papers, 1957-1994 M1759
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Audio Visual
  - Subseries 5: Color Adjustment
    - The Jeffersons, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 154)
    - Ozzie & Harriet Vol 1, Video: VHS (Box 116, Folder 154)
      2 episodes
    - Ozzie & Harriet Vol 4, Video: VHS (Box 116, Folder 154)
    - Dance Black America, Video: VHS; 90mins (Box 116, Folder 155)
      a festival of modern. Jazz, tap and african styles'
    - Good Times/Jeffersons, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 116, Folder 155)
    - Good Times, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 155)
    - Hill St Blues Pt 1, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 156)
    - Hill St Blues Pt 2, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 157)
    - The Jeffersons, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 158)
    - The Lucy Show, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 158)
      1 episode starring Jack Benny (1967)
    - Jack Benny, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 159)
      Jack Meets Mary Livingston' (1955) and 'Rochester gets the Bird' (1953)
    - Shokus Video Selection, Video: VHS (Box 116, Folder 159)
      Current Events, 1950s - Nixon;s checkers speech and 3 episodes of See it Now
    - CBS Game Show, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 116, Folder 160)
      WISK: "Baseball" first aired 14 Aug 1963 on 'Password' on CBS
    - WPA Film Library, Video: VHS (Box 116, Folder 161)
      Show reel
    - Amos n Andy 1, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 161)
      Amos n Andy 1
    - Amos n Andy 2, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 162)
      Amos n Andy 2
    - Nat King Cole, Video: VHS; 90mins (Box 116, Folder 163)
      Unforgettable - biography of Nat King Cole
    - The Honeymooners, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 116, Folder 164)
      Lost Episodes Vol 1
    - Hill St Blues, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 116, Folder 165)
    - Game Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 165)
      Episode of 'Take a Good Look' from 1959
    - Good Times/Jeffersons, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 116, Folder 166)
    - Good Times, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 166)
      Good Times Episode Production #302 - 'A Real Cool Job'
    - Hill St Blues, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 116, Folder 167)
      Hill Street Blues
    - Hill St Blues, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 167)
    - Hill St Blues, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 167)
    - The Jeffersons, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 168)
    - The Story of Television, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 168)
      RCA's corporate history of pre-1956 developments in television.
    - The Silent Enemy, Video: VHS; 90min (Box 116, Folder 168)
      Fictional Film - 1930 - about the life of Indians in Northern Canada portrayed by real Ojibway Indians - silent with score
    - Frank's Place, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 116, Folder 169)
    - Louisiana Story, Video: VHS; 80mins (Box 116, Folder 169)
      Film by Robert Flaherty in 1948 about a young cajun boy in the bayou
    - "We Interrupt this Program" - Roots Clips 1, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 117, Folder 170)
      From VHS - Beta xfer
    - Roots 1, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 170)
      Clips of 'Roots' - from VHS
    - Roots 2, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 171)
    - Roots 3, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 172)
    - Roots 4, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 173)
    - Roots 5, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 174)
    - Roots 6, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 175)
    - Roots 6 End, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 176)
    - TV Clips, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 176)
      Ozzie & Harriet, Cosby, Brady Bunch and Star Trek
    - Cosby/Brady Bunch/Star Trek, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 176)
    - Good Times/Brady Bunch, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 177)
    - Good Times/Brady Bunch, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 177)
    - Hogans Heroes/My 3 sons, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 178)
    - A Laugh/A Tear, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 178)
      Montage of TV clips of blacks in TV shows - with Voice Over by Whoopi Goldberg (and commercials)
    - Franks Place/Gilligans Island/Mr Ed, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 179)
    - Frank's Place, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 179)
    - Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 180)
      Cosby Show - 'Rich Girl' Episode
    - Cosby Show, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 180)
      Cosby Show - 'Rich Girl' Episode - also Hill St Blues
    - Franks Place, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 117, Folder 181)
    - Cosby Show/The New Mission Impossible, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 181)
    - Franks Place, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 182)
      Epsiode 'Frank joins the club' - Transfer from VHS
    - Franks Place, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 182)
    - Amos & Andy, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 183)
      Episode 'Rare Coin' - Film to tape transfer
    - Amos & Andy, Video: VHS (Box 117, Folder 184)
      Shokus Video - Amos n Andy Vol V - 4 episodes 1951/52
    - Amos & Andy, Video: VHS (Box 117, Folder 184)
      Shokus Video - Amos n Andy Vol VI - 4 episodes 1952/53
    - Amos & Andy, Video: VHS (Box 117, Folder 185)
      Shokus Video - Amos n Andy Vol IV - 4 episodes 1953
    - Amos & Andy, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 185)
      Clips from Episodes 'The Uranium Mine' and 'Father by Proxy'
    - TV Shows, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 185)
      Clips from: Gilligans Island, Donna Reed, and My Little Margie
    - Julia, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 186)
      Episode Production Number #4813
    - Julia, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 117, Folder 187)
      Episode Production Number #4815
    - Amos & Andy, Video: VHS (Box 117, Folder 188)
      Shokus Video - Amos n Andy Vol III - 4 episodes 1952
    - Network Fall Presentations, Video: VHS (Box 117, Folder 189)
      Shokus Video #402
    - TV Ads/Julia, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 117, Folder 190)
    - Original Film and Video Library footage, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 117, Folder 190)
      Window Dub: Selects 50s/60s TV shows
    - Steve Allen Show, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 118, Folder 191)
      Episodes with Diahann Carroll, 1959 and Dick Gregory, 1963
    - The Steve Allen Show, Video: VHS (Box 118, Folder 191)
      Show from 17 May 1959 featuring Diahann Carroll
    - Ed Sullivan, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 118, Folder 192)
    - Original Film and Video Library footage, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 192)
      Pilot Episode of Julia
    - I Spy, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 193)
      Episode #1 - 3/4inch transfer
    - I Spy, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 194)
      Episode #67 - 3/4inch transfer
    - I Spy, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 118, Folder 195)
      Episode #73 'Home to Judgement'
    - I Spy, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 196)
      Episode 'We Interrupt'
    - All in the Family Special, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 197)
      Selects 'Lady Liberty' and 'Jungle Bunnies'
    - All in the Family Special, Video: Umatic (Box 118, Folder 197)
    - All in the Family/Fresh Prince/Cosby, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 118, Folder 198)
    - All in the Family Special Pt 2, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 118, Folder 198)
    - Amos N Andy, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 199)
      Episode from 1952 'Cousin Effie's Will' - Original Film and Video Library
    - Clip Transfers, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 118, Folder 201)
      Clip Transfers from 3/4 inch: Hey Mulligan, Jack Benny, Lucy, Groucho, I Married Joan, Dragnet, Chvrolet commercial, Brylcream commercial, Eddie Fisher Coke Time
    - 1950s Show clips and commercials, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 118, Folder 201)
      Clips of Hey Mulligan, Jack Benny, Lucy, Groucho, I Married Joan, Dragnet, Chvrolet commercial, Brylcream commercial, Eddie Fisher Coke Time
    - Beulah Part 1, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 118, Folder 202)
      Episode 'Barbecue'
    - Beulah Part 2, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 118, Folder 203)
    - Beulah/Fugitive, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 118, Folder 204)
    - Game Show Program, Video: VHS (Box 118, Folder 205)
      Shokus Video #309 - episodes of 'You Bet Your Life' (1955), 'Beat the Clock' (1956), 'The $64,000 Question' (1956) and 'Queen for a Day' (1963)
    - Ozzie & Harriet, Video: Umatic (Box 118, Folder 205)
      Show opening for jet pilot episode
    - The Milton Berle Show, Video: VHS (Box 118, Folder 206)
      Shokus Video #237 - 2 episodes from 1951/54
    - Vintage Commercials, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 118, Folder 207)
      Shokus Video #404 - 60mins of classic television commercials from the 1950s and early 1960s
    - TV Variety, Video: VHS (Box 118, Folder 208)
      Shokus Video #421 - 'The Frank Sinatra Show' (1951), 'The Edsel Show' (1957), and an episode of 'The Honeymooners' (1952)
    - The Roy Rogers Show, Video: VHS (Box 118, Folder 209)
      Shokus Video #437 - 4 episodes from 1950
    - Amos & Andy, Video: VHS (Box 118, Folder 210)
      Shokus Video #705 - Amos n Andy Holiday Hour
    - Car 54 Where are You?, Video: VHS; 50mins (Box 118, Folder 211)
      2 episodes from 1961
    - Beulah, Video: Umatic (Box 119, Folder 212)
      Episode 'Rose Garden'
    - Beulah, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 213)
      Episode 'Beulah Helps the Henderson' - 3/4inch transfer
    - Dragnet, Video: Umatic; 10mins (Box 119, Folder 214)
      Film to tape transfer - Episode 'The Big Sound Off' - Main Title and Prologue only
    - Dragnet, Video: Umatic; 10mins (Box 119, Folder 214)
      Episode of Dragnet 'Big Sound Off' - opening monologue
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 215)
      Episode Production #203 - 3/4inch transfer
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 216)
      Episode Production #204 - 3/4inch transfer
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 217)
      Episode Production #305 - 3/4inch transfer
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 218)
      Episode Production #308 - 3/4inch transfer
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 219)
      Episode Production #108 - 3/4inch transfer
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 220)
      Episode Production #221 - 3/4inch transfer
    - All in the Family, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 221)
      Episode Production #715s - 3/4inch transfer
    - Jeffersons, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 222)
      from 3/4inch transfer
    - Diff'rent Strokes, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 223)
    - The Sanford Arms, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 224)
    - Television #1, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 225)
      Dub of 1inch tape
    - RKO-Pathe: Television 1939, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 119, Folder 225)
      Budget Films
    - Julia, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 226)
      Fred MacDonald Archive Transfer - Episodes 'Charlies Chance' and 'Christmas Show'
    - The Furst Family of Washington, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 227)
      Fred MacDonald Archive Transfer from 16mm
    - Eastside/Westside, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 228)
      Episode 'No Hiding Place' (Season 1- 1963) from 3/4inch transfer
    - Eastside/Westside, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 229)
      Episode 'Who do you Kill?' (Season 1- 1963) from 3/4inch transfer
    - That's My Mama, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 230)
    - What's Happening, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 231)
    - Television #2, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 119, Folder 232)
      Fred MacDonald Archive Transfer - Beulah, Sheena, Texaco Theatre
    - Footage, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 119, Folder 233)
      Video Resources Footage
    - Sanford & Son, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 234)
    - Eastside/Westside, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 119, Folder 2289)
      Episodes 'No Hiding Place' and 'Who do you Kill?' (Season 1- 1963)
    - Sanford & Son, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 234)
    - Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 235)
      Episode 'Lisa buys a car'
    - Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 236)
    - Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 237)
    - Dick Cavett Show, Video: VHS; 90mins (Box 120, Folder 238)
      Show #28 starring Diahann Carroll with Zero Mostel and Dr. David Hubbard
    - Color Adjustment - Different World, Video: Betacam; 20mins (Box 120, Folder 238)
      Episode 5-2
    - Good Times, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 239)
      Episode Production #101 - from 3/4inch transfer
    - Good Times, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 240)
      Episode Production #212 - from 3/4inch transfer
    - Good Times, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 241)
      Episode Production #216 - from 3/4inch transfer
    - Beulah, Video: Umatic (Box 120, Folder 242)
      Episode 'The Waltz' (Season 2 - 1952) - Hattie McDaniel, 10mins
    - Documentary clips, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 243)
      Documentary selections from 'The Life and Times of Rosie the Riveter' by Connie Fields and 'Anatomy of a Controversy' about the Amos & Andy show
    - Donna Reed, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 244)
    - Donna Reed, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 120, Folder 244)
    - Frank's Place, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 245)
    - Bill Cosby, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 246)
    - The Donna Reed Show/Hogans Heroes, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 120, Folder 247)
      Fred MacDonald Archives
    - The Jack Benny Program, Video: Betacam SP; 30mins (Box 120, Folder 248)
      UCLA Film Archive - Episode 'How Jack found Mary'
    - Television clips, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 120, Folder 249)
      Contains selections from 'Bewitched', 'Laverne & Shirley', 'Minstrel Days' and 'Amos & Andy' (Fred MacDonald Archive Transfer)
    - Television clips, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 120, Folder 250)
      Contains Selections from 'My Three Sons' and the 'Brady Bunch' (Fred MacDonald Archive Transfer)
    - My Three Sons, Video: Betacam (Box 120, Folder 251)
    - My Three Sons, Video: Umatic (Box 120, Folder 251)
    - Cosby Show, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 120, Folder 2367)
      Cosby Show 1 and 2
    - Family Affair/Gilligans Island, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 121, Folder 252)
    - Star Trek, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 121, Folder 253)
    - I Dream of Jeannie/Happy Days, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 121, Folder 254)
    - Ozzie & Harriet, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 121, Folder 255)
      Film Library footage of 'Ozzie & Harriet' and Eastman Kodak Company Openings
    - In Living Color, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 256)
    - The Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 257)
    - The Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 258)
    - Trouble with Father II, Video: VHS (Box 121, Folder 259)
      Shokus Video #262 - 4 episodes from 1952/3
    - The Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 260)
    - A Different World, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 261)
    - Amos & Andy, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 262)
      Clips of Amos n Andy
    - True Colors, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 263)
    - The Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 264)
    - Frank's Place, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 265)
    - In Living Color, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 266)
    - Television Selections, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 121, Folder 267)
      Episodes from 'Father Knows Best', 'My Little Margie' and 'I Married Joan'
    - Television Selections, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 121, Folder 268)
      Episodes from 'Leave it to Beaver', 'Captain Jack', 'Amos n Andy' (Cousin Effie's Will)
    - Julia, Video: Umatic (Box 121, Folder 269)
      Episodes 'Mama's Man' and 'The Interview' (Episodes #1 and 2, 1968)
    - Commercials, Video: VHS (Box 121, Folder 270)
      Video Supermarket Commcercials
    - Franks Place, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 121, Folder 271)
    - Fresh Prince of Bel Air, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 122, Folder 272)
    - Commercials, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 273)
      Commercials from Fred MacDonald Archive Transfer
    - Room 222, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 122, Folder 274)
      Episode #4902 'The Flu'
    - Ozzie & Harriet/Brady Bunch, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 275)
      Episode of Ozzie and Harriet 'An Evening with Hamlet' and The Brady Bunch - Pilot episode 'The Honeymoon'
    - The Waltons/Family Affair, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 276)
      Episode of The Waltons (pilot presentation highlights and Family Affair, pilot episode 'Buffy'
    - Andy Griffith/Amos n Andy, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 277)
      Episode of The Andy Griffith Show, episode 1 'The New Housekeeper' and the Amos n Andy show 'The Christmas Story'
    - The Debbie Reynolds Show, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 278)
    - Donna Reed, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 122, Folder 279)
    - Television Selections, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 122, Folder 280)
      3/4inch tape and 16mm film transfers: '69 Plymouth, Jello, Newport Cigarrettes, Uranium Mine, Father by Proxy, Andy needs eyeglasses, Crest, RCA Television and Kelvinator Refridgerator
    - The Cosby Show, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 122, Folder 281)
    - Fred MacDonald Archive, Video: VHS; 120mins (Box 122, Folder 282)
    - The Jack Benny Program, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 283)
      Video Yesteryear #348 - 2 episodes from 1954
    - Ozzie & Harriet, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 284)
      Video Yesteryear #655 - 2 episodes from 1964
    - Ozzie & Harriet, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 285)
      Video Yesteryear #621 - 2 episodes from 1966 'Walley the author' and 'Sheik of Araby'
    - Texaco Star Theatre, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 286)
      Video Yesteryear #792 - Episode from 1951
    - The Beulah Show, Video: VHS; 60mins (Box 122, Folder 287)
      Video yesteryear No.593 - 2 episodes of Beulah from 1952
    - TV Variety XXIV, Video: VHS (Box 122, Folder 288)
      Shokus Video #465 - Club Oasis and Frankie Laine Time
    - I Married Joan, Video: VHS; 50mins (Box 122, Folder 289)
      Video Yesteryear #841 - 2 episodes from 1955, 'Joans Testimonial Lunch' and 'The St Bernards'
    - Check and Double Check, Video: VHS; 80mins (Box 122, Folder 290)
      1930 - the only feature film with Amos n Andy and music by Duke Ellington
    - Good Times, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 122, Folder 298)
      Taped from TV
    - Family Matters, Video: Betacam SP (Box 122, Folder 299)
    - Archive Footage, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 123, Folder 401)
      Film footage from Petrified Films Inc (now Getty Images)
    - Archive Footage, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 123, Folder 402)
    - Fox Movietone news, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 403)
      Mix of ABC News from Sherman Grinberg Libraries including Vietnam protests and WWII footage transferred from film and tape
    - Stock Footage, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 404)
      WTN source
    - Civil Rights Stories, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 405)
    - Various stories, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 406)
      American Revolution of '63
    - NBC News Archives, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 407)
    - NBC News Archives, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 408)
      We Interrupt this program' featuring 3 historic TV News dramas
    - ABC News, Video: VHS; 30mins (Box 123, Folder 409)
      Archival footage from the Mississippi Department of Archives and History
    - Mississippi Archives, Video: Betacam; 5mins (Box 123, Folder 410)
    - Mississippi Archives, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 410)
      Also BIBA tape No718
    - KTVU Panthers, Video: Betacam SP (Box 123, Folder 411)
      Black Power, White Backlash
    - Film Archive footage, Video: Umatic (Box 123, Folder 4012)
      News footage from Fox Movietone News collection - 12mins running time
    - Berkley in the 60s, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 124, Folder 414)
      Archive films - Kenn Rabin (Archival and footage researcher)
    - Archive Films, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 124, Folder 415)
      Grinberg Pt1 of 3 - various news clips
    - Archive News, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 124, Folder 416)
      Grinberg Pt2 of 3 - various news clips
    - Archive News, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 124, Folder 417)
      Grinberg Pt3 of 3 - various news clips
    - Archive News, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 124, Folder 418)
      Grinberg Stock Footage - Pt 1 of 3
    - Archive Films, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 124, Folder 419)
      Grinberg Stock Footage - Pt 2 of 3
    - Archive Films, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 124, Folder 420)
      Grinberg Stock Footage - Pt 3 of 3
    - Archive Films, Video: Umatic; 10mins (Box 124, Folder 421)
      Anti-Integration Clips - Little Rock clip
    - UCLA Archive, Video: Umatic; 10mins (Box 124, Folder 422)
      NBC White Paper #2 Sit In
    - CBS News, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 124, Folder 4123)
      Black Panthers, MLK, Black Power - Footage from KPIX, KQED, KRON
    - NBC News, Video: Umatic; 20mins (Box 125, Folder 423)
      Film Transfer, 1991
    - National Archives, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 125, Folder 424)
    - Tomorrow TV - UCLA Archive, Video: Umatic (Box 125, Folder 425)
    - TV Commercials - Window Dub, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 125, Folder 427)
      RCA TV Commercials and early TV Broadcasts - from Video Resources, NY
    - KQED Tape Archives, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 125, Folder 428)
      Current Affairs - Various 1inch masters
    - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 125, Folder 432)
      Clips of Berkeley in the 60s and the Black Panthers (KPIX) - also BIBA Tape No. 716
    - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Betacam; 30mins (Box 125, Folder 433)
      Clips of Berkeley in the 60s - Archive Print Roll #3, KQED Reel of Black Panthers and Stokeley - also BIBA Tape No. 714
    - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Betacam (Box 125, Folder 434)
      Clips of Berkeley in the 60s and Martin Luther King Jnr -KPIX #6
    - KRON - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Betacam (Box 125, Folder 435)
      KRON Rolls 7 & 8 - 3/4inch tape transfer
    - KRON - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Betacam (Box 125, Folder 436)
      KRON Rolls 11 & 12 - 3/4inch tape transfer
    - Eyes on the Prize, Video: Betacam SP; 5mins (Box 125, Folder 437)
      Episode #5
    - Archive film, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 125, Folder 438)
      Grinberg stock footage - transferred on 08 Apr 1991
    - Archive film, Video: Umatic; 10mins (Box 125, Folder 439)
      Grinberg stock footage - transferred 09 Apr 1991
    - Archive film, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 125, Folder 440)
    - KRON, Video: Betacam; 10mins (Box 125, Folder 4356)
      KRON Rolls 7 & 8, 11 & 12 - 3/4inch tape transfer
    - KRON - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Umatic (Box 125, Folder 4356)
      KRON Rolls 7 & 8, 11 & 12 - Window Dub
    - CBS Pick Ups, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 125, Folder 42931)
      Clips of Little Rock and the March on Alabama State House
    - Berkeley in the 60s, Video: Umatic; 60mins (Box 125, Folder 432436)
      Footage from KPIX, KQED, KRON of Black Panthers, Carmichael, MLK and Oakland protests
    - CBS News, Video: Umatic (Box 126, Folder 441)
      Archive news clips of MLK Funeral, Boston Bussing and JR High
    - Archive Film, Video: Umatic; 40mins (Box 126, Folder 442)
      Grindberg stock footage - transferred 09 Apr 1991
    - Sherman Grindberg Stock Footage, Video: Umatic (Box 126, Folder 443)
    - Sherman Grindberg Stock Footage, Video: Umatic (Box 126, Folder 444)
    - NBC News, Video: Umatic; 30mins (Box 126, Folder 445)
      Archive news clips - transferred 10 Apr 1991
    - CBS news, Video: Umatic (Box 126, Folder 446)
      COJ #16 - Interview